<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>DAISY Accessible Publishing Knowledge Base</title>
		<description>Recent updates to the DAISY Accessible Publishing KB</description>
		<link>https://kb.daisy.org/publishing/docs</link>
		<copyright>2024 DAISY. All rights reserved</copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Thur, 19 Sept 2024 00:01:00 +0500</lastBuildDate>
		<pubDate>Thur, 19 Sept 2024 12:00:00 +0500</pubDate>
		<ttl>1440</ttl>
		
		<item>
			<title>New pages for QR codes</title>
			<link>https://kb.daisy.org/publishing/docs/html/images-qr.html</link>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[
				<p>Although QR codes are most often associated with getting people from physical to digital media,
					they are starting to appear in digital publications. QR codes can be helpful for devices that
					are not connected to the internet, but they need to be created accessibly to be useful to the
					greatest number of readers. The knowledge base now includes a page covering best practices for
					<a href="https://kb.daisy.org/publishing/docs/html/images-qr.html">QR codes</a>.</p>
				]]>	
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thur, 19 Sept 2024 12:00:00 +0500</pubDate>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>New pages for accessibility features</title>
			<link>https://kb.daisy.org/publishing/docs/metadata/schema.org/accessibilityFeature.html</link>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[
				<p>The knowledge base now includes separate pages for each of the schema.org 
					<code>accessibilityFeature</code> values. As the list of these values grows, maintaining
					their explanations in a single page has made discovering information about them more cumbersome.
					By breaking them out into separate pages, each value now includes more information and examples.</p>
				]]>	
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thur, 28 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0500</pubDate>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>New pages on setting the text direction</title>
			<link>https://kb.daisy.org/publishing/docs/epub/dir.html</link>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[
				<p>The knowledge base now includes two new pages covering the use of the <code>dir</code> attribute
					to set the base direction for text in the <a 
					href="https://kb.daisy.org/publishing/docs/epub/dir.html">package document</a> and in 
					<a href="https://kb.daisy.org/publishing/docs/html/dir.html">HTML documents</a>.</p>
				]]>	
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0500</pubDate>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>Expanded guidance on page navigation</title>
			<link>https://kb.daisy.org/publishing/docs/navigation/pagenav.html</link>
			<description>
				<![CDATA[
				<p>The page on page navigation is now split in four:</p>
				<ul>
					<li><a href="https://kb.daisy.org/publishing/docs/navigation/pagenav.html">Overview</a></li>
					<li><a href="https://kb.daisy.org/publishing/docs/navigation/pagebreaks.html">Page Breaks</a></li>
					<li><a href="https://kb.daisy.org/publishing/docs/navigation/pagelist.html">Page List</a></li>
					<li><a href="https://kb.daisy.org/publishing/docs/navigation/pagesrc.html">Page Source</a></li>
				</ul>
				<p>These pages provide additional context on their respective topics, as well as update and expand
					on the examples and frequently asked questions.</p>
				
				<p>Some of the new issues covered include not adding page breaks to headings, how to identify the
					source of pagination when the source does not have a unique identifier, and that preference
					should now be given to the <code>pageBreakSource</code> property.</p>
				]]>	
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thurs, 22 Feb 2024 12:00:00 +0500</pubDate>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
